Having fulfilled entered the game as our
ERP was, you know, quite a bit of a a
game-changer for us. Senior Director of
Supply Chain over here at Monos, so
everything from procurement all the way
out to, you know, fulfillment and
reverse logistics. Monos is a very
large-scale company. We do nine-figure
revenue across several regions of
operations. We're, you know, in North
America, we're in the EU, the UK,
Australia, and there are other couple of
burgeoning regions that we're on the
cusp of entering. Kind of weird to
imagine being where we are currently
having you guys as our ERP plus the
state of things currently with AI and
just, you know, just rewinding that
clock like 730 days and thinking or
1,000 days and thinking of how things
were back then, and, you know, that
period of time it seems like it's a lot
more due to the rate of change that's,
you know, transpired. I think the one
thing that, you know, I've been very
happy with with Fulfill is just rate of
change. It seems that there's constantly
Kaizen within your organization, the
fact that you're always trying to make
incremental changes throughout the
structure of the ERP itself. And, you
know, like as you, you know, have worked
with other large-scale ERPs, sometimes
you don't see that same iterative
change. And it it's nice to see that
progressive element, and I feel that it
really reflects the way that our
organization is as well. Really is an
organization that
seeks to constantly improve everything,
all our processes, just incrementally
day by day, always trying to find a
better way of doing things, and I I feel
like Fulfill definitely reflects that on
that side of things, and it's very much
a a matching spirit. Things like
inventory management was extremely
difficult before because everything was
living either on our 3PL's WMS exports
plus like our master Excel sheets that
we used to kind of combine that
information.
Whereas now we natively have it within,
you know, Fulfill itself where it should
be living. We've entered new regions,
we've entered new channels or we've
grown channels that we existedly did
business in. And like I would say that
over the past 18 months, there's been a
surge of complexity within our
organization from a supply chain
perspective, but despite that, we've
actually maintained the same head count
and managed to keep the same workload
for all of our employees effectively.
So, we're effectively doing more with
the same amount of people. I think one
of the greatest things about fulfill is
how aggressive you guys have been with
partner expansion.
Effectively, every potential partner
that we reach out to regarding a new
opportunity, you guys have already
they have some knowledge or experience
or they do actively work with you.
Right? So, you guys are a known you you
guys are definitely a known quantity
within our industry. And like whenever
we want to do the Amazon, for example,
whether it be 1P or FBA, you guys have,
you know, out-of-the-box integrations
that are very easy to to integrate and
plug into. Uh when we look to expand
with other 3PLs uh that are major
players, most of them, I would say at
least 80% of them have heard of you. Uh
and the 20% that have not tend to be, I
would call, more along the lines of like
old-school
3PLs, you know, like the mom-and-pop.
So, yeah, like whenever we want to
pursue an opportunity, it definitely is
better for us knowing that most of the
partners that we we seek these
opportunities with have some experience
with you. You guys are definitely like
hands-on. You guys really come, you
know, ready to like really ready to like
implement and to roll out. I think one
of the things that you guys probably
pitch and I I agree with is speed of
implementation. You know, with with any
of the larger or traditional ERPs, you
often find that to properly execute an
implementation, you're looking anywhere
from 6 months to 2 years, right? And it
can be an extremely painful, prolonged
process involving a lot of people across
a lot of functions within the
organization, but I find with you guys,
you deploy a very aggressive agile small
team, and you guys work with us very
aggressively to to push out these
deliverables in terms of the
implementation very quickly. So, like
your your implementation team um was
incredible. The people that we work
with, Luis was like one of the best
consultants we ever worked with, quite
frankly. And so, he was a true pleasure
to work with. And so, that the
implementation, the speed at which we
can roll out integrations, which means
speed that we can enter markets, the the
speed at which we can, you know, take
advantage of new opportunities. Like
we're looking at, you know, weeks, not
months, right? I was a huge fan of
NetSuite coming on board. I'm kind of
180'd, and I actually feel that a lot
has to do with just like how
incrementally you guys change things,
and just how open you guys are to
basically a lot of things that a lot of
other ERPs try to gatekeep. You guys are
especially effective for brands that are
like D2C and that are agile, that that
try to be tech-savvy and and
tech-leveraged, right? Like you guys
have always kind of like advertised
yourself in that way, and I feel like
there is a lot of truth to that. Like I
said, like as we explore po- possible
partnerships, whether it be like
channels or 3PL partners,
whenever we open conversations with
potential partners who are also, you
know, tech-savvy, uh tech-forward, and
moving in the direction of like, you
know, like leveraging AI, they all
have heard of you or are integrated with
you already,
right? So, like I I definitely feel like
that's one thing that people should keep
in mind. Like if if their organization
also values those same things.